Will Andrée

Designer and front-end developer with a sweeping background in the visual arts. Avid practitioner of phased prototyping and the iterative design process. Innate fondness for experimentation, and, above all, creating delightful experiences.

(573) 820-2616 williamandree@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/wi lliam-andree/

EXPERIENCE

Jubilant Digital Marketing, Overland Park, KS — Front-end Developer/Lead Designer

MARCH 2022 - AUGUST 2023

- Working in concert with clients and project manager, generated websites optimized for maximum web visibility. The wide scope of my work included website prototyping, brand retooling, and web development.
- As Lead Designer, produced brand style guides, new and redesigned logos, and designed web campaign ads.

Nucamp, Kansas City, MO — Web Development Instructor

AUGUST 2019 - MARCH 2022

Taught beginning-to-intermediate front-end development, from HTML/CSS, and JavaScript up to React.js. As an instructor I gave a weekly lecture and facilitated learning with class projects and weekly assignments.

Kemper Museum, Kansas City, MO — Retail Administrator

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MARCH 2017

Researched new products/product lines in accordance with retail trends and exhibition themes.

EDUCATION

Drury University, Springfield, MO

Art History with an emphasis on the history of Architecture, Art Criticism

Savannah College of Art and Design, Savannah, GA

Art and Art History fundamentals, Art Criticism

SKILLS

Graphic Design

UX Design

Trend Forecasting

Advanced Prototyping

Web Development (React, Vue, JavaScript/HTML/CSS, Sass, Wordpress Development)

TECH

Illustrator

Figma

Photoshop

Visual Studio

After Effects